Guide to the Manny Harriman Video Oral History Collection ALBA.VIDEO.048
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Manny Harriman Oral History Project
  - Geiser, Carl Interview, Apr 14, 1985 (Box 23, Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-051)
    Fifth of seven tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Carl Geiser discussing the history of Spanish Civil War POWs and his book project.
  - Geiser, Carl Interview, Apr 14, 1985 (Box 23, Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-053)
    Seventh of seven tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Carl Geiser discussing the history of Spanish Civil War POWs and his book project.
  - Geiser, Carl Interview, Apr 14, 1985 (Box 23, Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-052)
    Sixth of seven tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Carl Geiser discussing the history of Spanish Civil War POWs and his book project.
  - Giler, Henry Interview, Apr 5, 1985 (Box 23, Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-054)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Henry Giler.
  - Goff, Irving (Irv) Interview, Apr 3, 1985 (Box 23, Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-055)
    First of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irv Goff. Goff may be discussing fellow veterans Irving Fajans, Alex Kunstlich, Vincent Lossowski, Mike Jiminez, and Hymie[?] Jiminez.
  - Goff, Irving (Irv) Interview, Apr 3, 1985 (Box 23, Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-056)
    Second of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irv Goff. Goff may be discussing fellow veterans Irving Fajans, Alex Kunstlich, Vincent Lossowski, Mike Jiminez, and Hymie[?] Jiminez.
  - Goff, Irving (Irv) Interview, Apr 3, 1985 (Box 23, Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-057)
    Third of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irv Goff. Goff may be discussing fellow veterans Irving Fajans, Alex Kunstlich, Vincent Lossowski, Mike Jiminez, and Hymie[?] Jiminez.
  - Goff, Irving (Irv) Interview, undated (Box 23, Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-058)
    Fourth of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irv Goff. Goff may be discussing fellow veterans Irving Fajans, Alex Kunstlich, Vincent Lossowski, Mike Jiminez, and Hymie[?] Jiminez.
  - Goff, Irving (Irv) Interview; VALB Dinner Fundraiser for Nicaragua Ambulances, Apr 14, 1985 (Box 23, Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-059)
    Tape contains two events. Recording of VALB Fundraiser for Nicaragua ambulances (4/14/1985); and fifth of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irv Goff discussing German and Austrian guerillas (4/17/1985).
  - Gold, Irving Interview, Jan 26, 1987 (Box 5, Item ALBA V 48-060, Box 23)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irving Gold.
  - Shuldiner, Anne (Anna Goldman) Interview, Feb 4, 1987 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-061, Box 23)
    First of two tapes containing interview with American Medical Bureau nurse Anna Goldman, who served under the name Anne Shuldiner.
  - Shuldiner, Anne (Anna Goldman) Interview, Feb 4, 1987 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-062, Box 23)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with American Medical Bureau nurse Anna Goldman, who served under the name Anne Shuldiner.
  - Goldring, Benjamin (Ben) Interview, Aug 12, 1986 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-063, Box 23)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ben Goldring.
  - Goldstein, [Abraham] David Interview, Sep 21, 1986; cuid932 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-064, Box 19)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran David Goldstein.
  - Goldstein, Benjamin (Butch) Memorial, Sep 29, 1985; cuid933 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-065, Box 19)
    Recording of memorial service for Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Butch Goldstein.
  - Goldstein, Maynard Interview, Dec 18, 1986 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-066, Box 23)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Maynard Goldstein.
  - Goloff, Harry Interview, Nov 2, 1986; cuid934 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-067, Box 19)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Harry Goloff.
  - Gonshak, Samuel Interview, Dec 19, 1986 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-068, Box 23)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Samuel Gonshak.
  - Gottlieb, Albert (Al) Interview, Jul 28, 1985; cuid935 (Box 19, Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-069)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Al Gottlieb.
  - Graeber, Kenneth (Ken) Interview, May 1, 1985 (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-070, Box 23)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ken Graeber.
  - Grell, Fritz discussed by LaVerne Grell; Perley Payne, Jr. Interview, undated (Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-071, Box 23)
    Tape contains two interviews. Second of two tapes containing interview with LaVerne Grell, son of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Fritz Grell; and interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Perley Payne, Jr.
  - Grumet, Leonard discussed by Donna Bemiss, Jul 28, 1985 (Box 23, Box 6, Item ALBA V 48-072)
    Interview with Donna Bemiss, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Leonard Grumet, who died July 9, 1959.
  - Haggerty, George discussed by Alice Haggerty, Jul 11, 1986 (Box 24, Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-073)
    Interview with Alice Haggerty, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran George Haggerty.
  - Hakam, Harry Interview, Jul 12, 1986 (Box 24, Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-074)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Harry Hakam.
  - Hakam, Harry Interview, Aug 15, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-075, Box 24)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Harry Hakam.
  - Harris, Sidney (Sid) discussed by Paul Harris and Manny Harriman, undated (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-076, Box 24)
    Discussion between Manny Harriman and Paul Harris, son of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sid Harris, about son's view of his father.
  - Hautaniemi, Joseph Interview, Sep 3, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-077, Box 24)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Joseph (Joe) Hautaniemi.
  - Heinricher, Stanley Interview, Feb 23, 1987 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-078, Box 24)
    First of three tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Stanley Heinricher.
  - Heinricher, Stanley Interview, Feb 23, 1987 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-079, Box 24)
    Second of three tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Stanley Heinricher.
  - Heinricher, Stanley Interview, Feb 23, 1987 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-080, Box 24)
    Third of three tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Stanley Heinricher.
  - Heisler, Gus Interview, Aug 14, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-081, Box 24)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Gus Heisler.
  - Heisler, Gus Interview, Aug 14, 1986 (Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-082, Box 24)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Gus Heisler.
  - Hill Liebert, Josephine Interview, Jun 11, 1986 (Box 24, Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-083)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade x-ray technician Josephine Hill, who may have served under the name Josephine Liebert.
  - Hinman, Loyal (Luke) Interview, Sep 7, 1985 (Box 24, Box 7, Item ALBA V 48-084)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Luke Hinman.
  - Holborn, Harry Interview, Jun 27, 1985 (Box 24, Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-085)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Harry Holborn.
  - Hollander, Herman (Hy) Interview, Feb 12, 1987 (Box 24, Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-086)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Hy Hollander.
  - Holtzman, Benjamin (Ben) Interview, Sep 13, 1986 (Box 24, Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-087)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ben Holtzman.
  - Hovan, John Interview, Sep 4, 1986 (Box 24, Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-088)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran John Hovan.
  - Junas, Stanely (Stan) Interview, May 3, 1986; cuid936 (Box 24, Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-089)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Stan Junas.
  - Katzman, Samuel (Sam) Interview, Apr 9, 1986 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-090, Box 24)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sam Katzman.
  - Poling, Eugene Interview; Sidney (Sid) Kaufman Interview, undated (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-091, Box 24)
    Tape contains two interviews. Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Eugene Poling, and third of three tapes containing interview with Sid Kaufman.
  - Kaye, George Interview, Aug 23, 1985 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-092, Box 24)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran George Kaye.
  - Keenan, Thomas Interview, Jan 25, 1987 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-093, Box 24)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Thomas Keenan.
  - Keir Jr., Duncan Interview; Clifton Amsbury Interview; Samuel Mendelowitz (Curley Mende) Interview, undated (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-094, Box 24)
    Tape contains three interviews. Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Duncan Keir, Jr.; interview with veteran Clifron Amsbury; and interview with Samuel (Sam) Mendelowitz, who was also known as Curley Mende.
  - Keller, Fred Interview, Apr 2, 2985 (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-095, Box 24)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Fred Keller.
  - Keller, Fred Interview; Sidney (Sid) Kaufman Interview, undated (Box 8, Item ALBA V 48-096, Box 24)
    Tape contains two interviews. Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Fred Keller; and first of three tapes containing interview with veteran Sid Kaufman.
  - Simon, John discussed by Ruth Simon; Hyman (Hy) and Ruth Rosner Interview; and Armand Keossian (Arnold Kerin) Interview, undated; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-097, Box 24, Dvd 1)
    Tape contains three interviews[?]. Interview with Ruth Simon, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran "Doc" John Simon; interview with veteran Hy Rosner and his wife, Ruth Rosner; and first of two interviews with veteran Armand Keossian (Arnold Kerin).
  - Keossian, Armand (Arnold Kerin) Interview; Rudolph (Rudy) Corbin Interview, undated; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-098, Box 24, Dvd 1)
    Tape contains two interviews. Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Armand Kerin[?]; and first of two tapes containing interview with veteran Rudy Corbin.
  - Koslow, Al Interview, Nov 28, 1986; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-099)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Al Koslow.
  - Kramer, Jacob (Jack) Interview, Feb 28, 1986; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-100)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Jack Kramer.
  - Kutnik, Lee Interview, Jul 16, 1985; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-101)
    Interview with San Francisco Friends of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade organizer[?] Lee Kutnik.
  - Landis, Arthur Interview, Jan 14, 1985; cuid937 (Box 19, Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-102)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Arthur Landis.
  - Landis, Arthur Interview; Irving (Irv) Goff Interview, Jan 16, 1985; cuid938 (Box 19, Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-103)
    Tape contains two interviews. Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Arthur Landis; and sixth of six tapes containing interview wi veteran Irv Goff. [Goff interview may be duplicate of an interview on V 48-055-59.]
  - Levine, Benjamin (Lane) Interview, May 3, 1986; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 24, Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-104)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Benjamin Levine, also known as Ben Lane.
  - Lee, Harold Interview, Apr 7, 1986; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-105)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Harold Lee.
  - Lending, Edward (Ed) Interview, Feb 7, 1987; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-106)
    First of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ed Lending.
  - Lending, Edward (Ed) Interview, Feb 7, 1987; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-107, Box 24, Dvd 1)
    Second of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ed Lending.
  - Lending, Edward (Ed) Interview, Feb 7, 1987; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 9, Item ALBA V 48-108)
    Third of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ed Lending.
  - Lending, Edward (Ed) Interview, Feb 7, 1987; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-109, Box 24, Dvd 1)
    Fourth of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ed Lending.
  - Lending, Edward (Ed) Interview, Feb 7, 1987; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-110, Box 24, Dvd 1)
    Fifth of five tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ed Lending.
  - Levine, Sidney (Sid) Interview, Jul 25, 1985; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-111, Box 24, Dvd 1)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sid Levine.
  - Levine, Sidney (Sid) Interview, Jul 26, 1985; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-112, Box 24, Dvd 1)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sid Levine.
  - Lloyd, Thomas (Tom) Interview, Sep 8, 1986; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-113, Box 24, Dvd 1)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Tom Lloyd.
  - Love, Vaughn Interview, Aug 27, 1986; cuid939 (Box 19, Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-114)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Vaughn Love. Includes a viewing copy.
  - Love, Vaughn Interview, Aug 28, 1986; cuid940 (Box 19, Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-115)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Vaughn Love.
  - Lucid, John (Jack) discussed by Kirsten and Robert Lucid, undated; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-116, Box 24, Dvd 1)
    Interview with Kirsten Lucid, wife of, and Robert Lucid, son of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Jack Lucid.
  - Malbin, Virginia Interview; Sidney (Sid) Kaufman Interview, undated; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-117)
    Tape contains two interviews. Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran (or nurse) Virginia Malbin; and second of three tapes containing interview with veteran Sid Kaufman.
  - Harris Marantz, Ray Interview, undated; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-118)
    Interview with American Medical Bureau nurse Ray Marantz, who served under the name Ray Harris.
  - McCarthy, Bill Interview, Aug 25, 1985; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-119)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Bill McCarthy.
  - MacLeod, Donald (Don) Interview; Fritz Grell discussed by LaVerne Grell, undated; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 10, Item ALBA V 48-120)
    Tape contains two interviews. Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Don MacLeod; and first of two tapes containing interview with LaVerne Grell, son of veteran Fritz Grell.
  - McDaniels, Eluard Luchell Interview, Aug 26, 1985; cuid941 (Box 19, Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-121)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Eluard Luchell McDaniels. User copy available
  - Madigan, Frank Memorium, May 1, 1986; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-122)
    Recording of memorial service for Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Frank Madigan.
  - Merriman, Marian Wachtel Interview, Sep 9, 1985; cuid942 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-123, Box 19)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Marian Wachtel Merriman.
  - Merriman, Robert (Bob) discussed by Marian Wachtel Merriman, Sep 9, 1985; cuid943 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-124, Box 19)
    Interview with Marian Wachtel Merriman about Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Bob Merriman.
  - Minor, Ben Interview, Sep 8, 1986; cuid944 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-125, Box 19)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ben Minor.
  - Mitchell, Irving Interview, Mar 6, 1986; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-126)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irving Mitchell.
  - Nelson, Steve Interview, Aug 30, 1986; cuid945 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-127, Box 19)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Steve Nelson. User copy available
  - Nelson, Steve Interview, Aug 30, 1986; cuid946 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-128, Box 19)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Steve Nelson. User copy available
  - Nitzberg, Leo discussed by Judy Nitzberg, Jul 9, 1985; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-129)
    Interview with Judy Nitzberg, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Leo Nitzberg. May also contain interview of his son.
  - Nitzberg, Leo discussed by Mariam Johnson, May 3, 1986; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-130, Box 24, Dvd 1)
    Interview with Mariam Johnson, friend of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Leo Nitzberg, who died in 1981. Mariam Johnson reads the eulogy she delivered at his memorial service.
  - Norton, Thomas (Tom) Interview, Jul 18, 1985; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-131)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Tom Norton.
  - Nusser, Charles Interview, undated; cuid947 (Box 11, Item ALBA V 48-132)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Charles Nusser.
  - Olsen, Leonard Interview, Jul 12, 1985; cuid948 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-133)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Leonard Olsen.
  - O'Malley, Thomas Interview, Aug 31, 1986; cuid949 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-134)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Thomas O'Malley.
  - Parker, Max discussed by Mary Parker, Aug 25, 1986; cuid950 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-135)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Mary Parker, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Max Parker.
  - Parker, Max discussed by Mary Parker, Aug 25, 1986; cuid951 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-136)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Mary Parker, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Max Parker.
  - Payne, Earle Interview, May 2, 1986; cuid952 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-137)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Earle Payne.
  - Peck, Samuel (Sam) Interview, Feb 6, 1987; cuid953 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-138)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sam Peck.
  - Perlman, Norman (Norm) Interview, Feb 22, 1986; cuid954 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-139)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Norm Perlman.
  - Perrone, John Interview, 1986-1987?; cuid955 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-139a)
  - Persilly, Coleman Interview, undated; cuid956 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-140)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Coleman Persilly.
  - Pike, William W. Interview, Aug 13, 1986; cuid957 (Box 19, Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-141)
    Interview with American Medical Bureau physician Dr. William W. Pike.
  - Postek, Stanley Interview, Jun 27, 1985; 1 videodisc (dvd) (Box 24, Dvd 1, Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-142)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Stanley Postek.
  - Prago, Albert Interview, Aug 14, 1986; cuid958 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-143)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Al Prago.
  - Rappaport, Irving William Interview, Jan 27, 1987; cuid959 (Box 12, Item ALBA V 48-144)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Irving Rappaport.
  - Reed, Robert L. Interview, Sep 4, 1985; cuid960 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-145)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Robert Reed.
  - Rigamonte, Gino Interview, Aug 5, 1985; cuid961 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-146)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Gino Rigamonte.
  - Bell, Hilda (Roberts) Interview, May 4, 1986; cuid962 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-149, Box 19)
    Interivew with American Medical Bureau nurse Hilda Bell Roberts, who served under the name Hilda Bell.
  - Robbins, Albert (Al) Interview, Dec 17, 1986; cuid963 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-147)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Al Robbins.
  - Robbins, Albert (Al) Interview, Jan 4, 1987; cuid964 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-148)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Al Robbins.
  - Rollins, Wade Interview, Aug 25, 1985; cuid965 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-150, Box 19)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Wade Rollins.
  - Romer, Edna Interview, Mar 12, 1986; cuid966 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-151)
    Interivew with American Medical Bureau nurse Edna Romer.
  - Romer, Samuel (Sam) discussed by Edna Romer, Mar 12, 1986; cuid967 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-152)
    Interview with Edna Romer, wife of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sam Romer.
  - Klein, Herman (Gabby) Interview, Apr 4, 1985; cuid968 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-153)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Herman (Gabby) Klein.
  - Klein, Herman (Gabby) Rosenstein Interview, Mar 3, 1986; cuid969 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-154)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Herman Rosenstein, who served under the name Herman (Gabby) Klein.
  - Ross, Adolph Interview, Aug 23, 1986; cuid970 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-155)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Adolph Ross.
  - Schiff, Samuel (Sam) Interview, Dec 4, 1986; cuid971 (Box 13, Item ALBA V 48-156)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sam Schiff.
  - Schlekau, Walter Interview, Jul 6, 1985; cuid972 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-157)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Walter Schlekau.
  - Schneider, Theodore (Ted) Interview, Dec 22, 1986; cuid973 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-158)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ted Schneider.
  - Schwerner, Moses (Murray) Interview, Apr 12, 1985; cuid974 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-159)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Murray Schwerner, who served under the name Moses Schwerner.
  - Secundy, Louis Interview, Dec 17, 1986; cuid975 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-160)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Louis Secundy.
  - Sennett, William Interview; Frank Brown Interview, Jun 24, 1985; cuid976 (Box 19, Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-161)
    Tape contains two interviews. Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran William Sennett; and interview with veteran Frank Brown. Use Copy available
  - Shafran, Jack Interview, Nov 15, 1986; cuid977 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-162)
    First of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Jack Shafran.
  - Shafran, Jack Interview, undated; cuid978 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-163)
    Second of two tapes containing interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Jack Shafran.
  - Shaker, Kenneth (Ken) Interview, undated; cuid979 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-164)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Ken Shaker.
  - Shosteck, Sidney discussed by Lawrence Darow Gurewitz, undated; cuid980 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-165)
    Interview with Lawrence Darow Gurewitz, cousin of Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Sidney Shosteck.
  - Shufer, Max Interview, Sep 28, 1986; cuid981 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-166)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Max Shufer.
  - Simon, John Leopold Interview, Nov 16, 1986; cuid982 (Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-167)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran John Simon.
  - Rackley, Mildred (Simon) Interview; Maurice Friedman discussed by Muriel Eldridge, undated; cuid983 (Box 19, Box 14, Item ALBA V 48-168)
    Tape contains two interviews. Interview with American Medical Bureau nurse Mildred Rackley Simon, who served under the name Mildred Rackley; and interview with Muriel Eldridge, sister of veteran Maurice Friedman.
  - Smith, Randall B. (Pete) Interview, Jul 30, 1986; cuid984 (Box 15, Item ALBA V 48-169)
    Interview with Abraham Lincoln Brigade veteran Randall B. (Pete) Smith.